export default [
  {
    question: 'Who is the father of computers ?',
    answers: [
      'Allen Turing',
      'Charles Babbage',
      'Timur Cary d',
      'Augusta Adams',
    ],
    correct_answer: 'Charles Babbage',
  },
  {
    question: 'Who is the father of computer science ?',
    answers: [
      'Allen Turing',
      'Charles Babbage',
      'Timur Cary d',
      'Augusta Adams',
    ],
    correct_answer: 'Allen Turing',
  },

  {
    question: 'Who is the father of personal Computers?',
    answers: [
      'Edward Robert',
      'Charles Babbage',
      'Timur Cary d',
      'None of these',
    ],
    correct_answer: 'Edward Robert',
  },
  {
    question: 'RAM stands for?',
    answers: [
      'Read Only Memory',
      'Random Access Memory',
      'Read-only memory',
      'None of these',
    ],
    correct_answer: 'Random Access Memory',
  },
  {
    question: '1 byte =',
    answers: ['2 bits', '4 bits', '8 bits', '1 bits'],

    correct_answer: '8 bits',
  },
  {
    question: 'The brain of any computer is ?',
    answers: ['ALU', 'CPU', 'Mouse', 'Keyboard'],

    correct_answer: 'Mouse',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following is used as primary storage device ?',
    answers: ['RAM', 'Harddisk', 'Floppy', 'All the above'],

    correct_answer: 'RAM',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following is hardware and not software ?',
    answers: ['Excel', 'CPU', 'Printer driver', 'Operating system'],

    correct_answer: 'CPU',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is MP3?',
    answers: ['A mouse', 'A printer', 'A scanner', 'A sound format'],

    correct_answer: 'A sound format',
  },
  {
    question: 'All deleted files go to -"',
    answers: ['Recycle bin', 'Taskbar', 'Toolbar', 'My computer'],

    correct_answer: 'Recycle bin',
  },
];
